#### SUMMARY

Passionate Web Developer seeking challenging opportunity. Background includes extensive experience in volunteer and cooperative environment with strong teambuilding. Passionate programmer who is self-motivated and enjoys new experiences and challenges.

### **PROFILE**

A detail-oriented programmer with experience in constructing web-based application and writing an application that makes use of common business information system environments. IT professional who has knowledge on creating graphical user interfaces and an application that demonstrates the principle of object-oriented design. Skills include: HTML, React, CSS, C#, .NET, SQL, Transact-SQL, Object Oriented Design, Relational Database Design, PHP, JavaScript, Jquery, NVM, GIT, Composer, Gulp

#### **EDUCATION**

Metropolitan State University, Minneapolis, MN Master's in Management Information Systems

Hennepin Technical Community College, Eden Prairie, MN Associates in .Net Programmer

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Web Developer, Fortra, December 2020 - Present

- Have experience in different CMS: Drupal, Wordpress, MODX
- Lead a wordpress upstreaming project
- Develop new capabilities for the Drupal and Wordpress sites
- Maintain site configurations and stability through debugging
- Work on front and back end development, along with theming
- Detail oriented when it comes down to web development
- Have built web pages using HTML/ CSS/ SCSS/ Javascript (React)/ Bootstrap
- Develop custom javascript to pull in the data from drupal paragraph types
- Configure gulp and composer in visual studio code for multiple websites
- Provide end-user support and training, and develop processes, procedures, and resources
- Perform duties including researching, designing, documenting and modifying application specifications throughout the product lifecycle

Web Developer, Web Hamster, MN, July 2020 – December 2020

- Design and develop web pages
- Handling all verbal and written communications between hosting companies, clients, and vendors.
- Edit icons and images on illustrator and photoshop

Web Development Internship, HELPSYSTEMS, Eden Prairie, MN 2019 – May 2020

- Create website layout/user interfaces by using standard HTML/CSS/JavaScript/jQuery
- Implement JavaScript library on pages
- Create doted navigation bar
- Develop forms using PHP

Web Developer Volunteer, Hosteling International, Miami, FL 2017 – 2019

- Designed and develop web pages
- Installed plugin to upload video in WordPress
- Created website layout/user interfaces by using standard HTML/CSS
- Gathered and refined specifications and requirements based on technical need
- Checked plugins and maintained website on various tasks
- Tested various features of web application
- Tracked and troubleshooted web application problems
- Created and maintained software documents

# CERTIFICATE

- CI/ CD with GitLab
- Leading and Working in Teams